https://www.pawschicago.org/privacy-policy/

Home
Our WorkHow To HelpEvents & Dog TrainingNews & ResourcesNo Kill MissionAbout Us
Pet AdoptionPets AvailableAdopt a CatAdopt a DogAdoption ProcessWhy AdoptAdoption CentersAdoption EventsA Pet's Journey Through PAWSOngoing Training & SupportRecently Adopted PetsPAWS AlumniSpay/NeuterLifesaving ImpactBenefits of Spay/NeuterSpay/Neuter ServicesLurie ClinicGusMobile Spay/Neuter VanFeral Cats (TNR)Importance of Early Spay/NeuterCommunity EngagementPAWS for Life OutreachCommunity CatsPAWS Chicago MagazineCrisis SupportGiving Up Your PetCOVID-19 Crisis Foster CareDisaster ResponsePetition to Stop Illegal Animal Importing
VolunteerBecome a VolunteerVolunteer OpportunitiesJunior VolunteersVolunteers of the MonthVolunteers of the YearDonateHoliday Giving 2020Your Giving Saves LivesLifeline Monthly Giving ProgramTributes and MemorialsCorporate GivingGuardian Angel Planned GivingCreate Your Own FundraiserOther Ways to GiveCreate Your Own (CYO) Fundraiser ProgramTEAM PAWS ChicagoAbout TEAM PAWS ChicagoFosterResources for FostersFind the Right Foster Pet for YouPets Available for FosteringFoster Call Tree Registration
Fundraising EventsAnimal MagnetismBeach PartyBeachBodTEAM PAWSFur BallTreat YourselfDesktop CalendarCommunity EventsAdoption EventsPet Loss HEAL Support GroupDog Training ClassesMeet the TrainersTraining Center
FAQs
News & FeaturesPAWS Chicago NewsNewsletterPAWS Chicago TodayAnimal WelfareFor Your PetPAWS Chicago MagazineFor People Who Love PetsAll About DogsDoggy BasicsGetting Started - A Guide for Bringing Home a New DogPreparing Your Dog for a Change in the FamilyUnderstanding Dog BehaviorMedical Care for Your DogProviding for Your Dog Should Something Happen To YouHow Dogs AgeProtocolsAll About CatsKitty BasicsGetting Started - A Guide for Bringing Home a New CatPreparing Your Cat for a Change in the FamilyUnderstanding Cat BehaviorMedical Care for Your CatProviding for Your Cat Should Something Happen To YouCat ResourcesResourcesChicago Area Animal SheltersFinding Your Lost PetHelping a Stray or Lost AnimalCoping with Pet LossHazardous Items for Pets
About No KillHistory of ShelteringThe No Kill RevolutionDefining No KillNo Kill Gold StandardThe No Kill ModelThe Foundation - Community EngagementThe Four PillarsA Model No Kill CommunityBuilding a No Kill ChicagoCommunity Results to DateAnimal Care & Control ResultsPAWS Chicago's ProgressionNo Kill Policy Recommendations
The StoryOur HistoryTimelines & MilestonesMission & ValuesWatch Our StoryResultsAdoption ProgramSpay/Neuter DataCommunity EngagementFinancial Health and SustainabilityLeadershipBoard of DirectorsDevelopment BoardProfessional BoardMedia CenterPAWS in the MediaMedia ArchiveVideo Archive
Building No Kill Communities!
Close Menu
Menu
DONATE
ADOPT
Home Page Privacy Policy
Share page:
Privacy Policy1. Disclosure of Customer Information
PAWS Chicago will not disclose any nonpublic personal information, except as permitted by law (in order to comply with federal or state laws/regulations, and government or court orders).
2. Disclosure of Donor Information
PAWS Chicago will not trade, share or sell a donor’s personal information with anyone else, nor send donor mailings on behalf of other unaffiliated organizations unless the donor has given PAWS specific permission to do so.
3. Collection, Retention, and Use of Information
PAWS Chicago collects nonpublic personal information about you from the forms we receive from you. PAWS Chicago will only collect information as we believe is reasonably useful in administering our business and to provide products, services and other opportunities to adopters/donors.
4. Maintenance of Accurate Information
PAWS Chicago will correct known inaccurate information in a timely manner.
5. Employee Access to Information and Enforcement
All PAWS Chicago employees are educated on the importance of confidentiality and customer privacy. They are thoroughly trained to learn and follow the PAWS Chicago Privacy Policy. Employees with access to adopter/donor information are required to adhere to the Privacy Policy.Any employees that violates the Privacy Policy will be subject to disciplinary measures (warnings, reprimands, suspensions) and possible termination of employment. Employees of PAWS Chicago will only have access to adopter/donor information on a need-to-know basis.6. Internet Information
PAWS Chicago recognizes the trust you have placed in us and the related responsibility we have regarding your privacy. It is PAWS Chicago’s responsibility to keep your sensitive personal information confidential. PAWS Chicago always has had formal procedures to help protect your privacy. With the surge in Internet use, it has become even more crucial that steps are taken to assure you that your private information remains private. PAWS Chicago Privacy Policy Principles include website privacy and control over your personal information.
Website Privacy
When any person visits the public areas of the website, certain basic information is collected, such as how many people visited the site and what pages were visited. Also included in the PAWS Chicago website is the capability for you to correspond with PAWS employees. This correspondence via e-mail may be for the purpose of asking general questions, requesting literature, or volunteering. These activities may include sharing some personal information about yourself with PAWS Chicago. E-mail addresses from those who correspond with PAWS Chicago are collected along with any other information you provide, for example site registration or survey information. Whether you are an adopter/donor of PAWS Chicago, personal information will be collected from you if, and only if, you voluntarily provide that information.
Further information regarding the PAWS Chicago Privacy Policy . This statement addresses our policies on Internet information and internal customer information. Additional inquiries and/or comments should be addressed to: Customer Relations, PAWS Chicago, 1933 N. Marcey Street, Chicago, IL 60614
